B1 Listen to Millie and Toby talking about lunchtime at Sunshine Middle School and Toby's school in the USA and fill in the blanks in the table below.
Hey Toby, is our lunchtime different from yours in the USA?
Yes, in the USA we only get half an hour for lunch, but here you get an hour and a half.
Oh yes, we have some time to relax after the meal.
Do you like the food in the dining hall?
I love it!
The dining hall here is full of delicious hot food and there are different dishes every day.
Back home, we only have a few to choose from, such as hamburgers, pizza, fried chicken and salad.
Sometimes we take our lunch to school in a lunchbox and eat it in the classroom. Really?
What kind of food do you take to school?
Just a sandwich and a snack like fruit or cookies.
Oh, so you can choose food to your taste here?
Yes, it's great!